<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Product Hunt Daily Hot</title><link>https://your-website-url.com</link><description>Daily hot products from Product Hunt</description><language>zh-cn</language><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 08:25:37 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Instant SEO Audit</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/instant-seo-audit?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>Check your website's SEO score instantly &amp; boost traffic

Instant SEO Audit is a Chrome extension that allows you to check your website's SEO score instantly &amp; boost traffic. It provides a detailed audit with all the action steps you need to boost your SEO score.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>WPS Office</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/wps-office-3?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>AI-Powered Office Suite for Everyone

WPS Office is an AI-powered office suite that makes AI easily accessible in everyday work for everyone, without expensive costs. Reshape your office workflow with AI copilot for writing, creating PPTs, spell check, translation, chatting with PDFs, and more.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>Ente Auth</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ente-auth?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>Free, Secure, Open Source 2FA

Ente Auth is an open source, cross platform 2FA app designed to offer a great experience for your two factor codes. With features like encrypted backups, next code, multi-device sync, sharing, notes, Ente Auth is recommended by CERN, LinusTechTips and more!</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>Sparrow</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/sparrow-7?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>The Open Source API Testing Tool For All Developers

Sparrow is a powerful API dev tool designed to simplify API testing and documentation. With features like powerful AI assistant, Automated API test flows and seamless document generation, it streamlines your dev workflow and enhances your team productivity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>Google Illuminate</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/google-illuminate-2?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>Transform research papers into AI-generated audio summaries

Transform research papers into AI-generated audio summaries with Illuminate, your Gen AI tool for understanding complex content faster.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>Gitfyel</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/gitfyel?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>Craft stunning GitHub profiles effortlessly.

The GitHub Readme Generator simplifies creating your GitHub profile. You can easily format your content, add stats, and showcase badges that highlight your skills and achievements. This tool helps you create a standout profile with minimal effort.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>Ant Browser for Apple Watch</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ant-browser-for-apple-watch?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>The web, wrist-sized. Helping you go phone-free.

Search the web on your Watch - Look up movie times, compare prices, or get the latest sports results—all without needing to pull out your phone.&amp;nbsp;</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>Temporal</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/temporal-2?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>Intelligent capacity planner for teams

Track vacations, sick leaves, birthdays, anniversaries and other notable events for your team members. Manage team schedules, project assignments, plan headcounts and allocate resources efficiently. Never be caught off-guard by staffing bottlenecks again.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>NPM Chart</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/npm-chart?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>Search for a npm package to see its download stats over time

Visualize npm downloads in a beautiful chart, ready to be shared with your community.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>The Ultimate Ebook about Design Systems</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-ultimate-ebook-about-design-systems?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>World-Class Ebook and Design System to Supercharge Design!

This e-book is your complete guide to creating and managing Design Systems in Figma, with best practices, tools, and hands-on tasks. Save time with all the resources you need in one place, crafted from years of experience. I’ll guide you every step of the way!</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>Fast-Music-Remover</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/fast-music-remover?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>A lightweight audio enhancer for internet media

A free and open-source, lightweight music and noise remover for internet media, powered by DeepFilterNet for audio enhancement. A minute-long video is processed in less than 5 seconds! Watch the demo at: https://github.com/omeryusufyagci/fast-music-remover</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>Attend QR</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/attend-qr?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>An attendance management system

Attend QR is an Attendance Management System where users scan Attend QR code to mark attendance in real time. Admins get detailed insights and reports. Automations and customizations can be made as per requirements.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>GoodWay Sprite Generator</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/goodway-sprite-generator?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>Magically transform Figma icons into sprite sheets with JSON

GoodWay Sprite Generator plugin turns selected icons into sprite sheets with JSON metadata. It generates a PNG sprite and a JSON file with icon sizes and coordinates, ideal for developers and designers working on web projects or UI libraries.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>guilds.me</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/guilds-me?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>Find Your Dream Discord Server With A Simple Search

Discover and join the perfect Discord communities with guilds.me. Explore a vast selection of servers and grow your own community effortlessly with our advanced tools.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>featureNest</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/featurenest?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>Easily capture, organize, and prioritize feature requests

FeatureNest is a cost-effective tool that helps teams centralize, categorize, and manage feature requests across multiple projects. Streamline collaboration, stay organized, and scale effortlessly with ease.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Live - Never miss a dip</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/bitcoin-price-live-never-miss-a-dip?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>Want to buy bitcoin cheaply? Get bitcoin drop alert!

Bitcoin Price Live browser extension shows the current Bitcoin price and alerts you to significant drops - great for buying opportunities. Customize alerts by setting drop size and time frame to monitor major changes and skip minor fluctuations.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>MindR</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/mindr-2?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>Your AI powered second brain on Telegram.

Ever stumbled upon a great idea, thought or some random musings only to forget it later? MindR remembers everything for you. Just send it anything you want to keep, then chat with it naturally whenever you need to recall.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>Turbo Generate</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/turbo-generate?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>Generate Text, Audio and Images in 1 Click with AI

Generate text, audio and images in 1 click with artificial intelligence tools. Start your Free Trial!</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>Optimal Health System</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/optimal-health-system?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>Manage your entire health.

The Notion Optimal Health System provides all the essential tools to take control of your health, manage it, and make it a priority in your life.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>AutoBacklink</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/autobacklink?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>Pr*ductHunt is sucks, let's promote each other's products!🤘

Automatically embed backlinks to your landing page and effortlessly market your product on other people's landing pages.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>Startup Levels</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/startup-levels?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>A competitive startup leaderboard to get traffic + backlink

Boost traffic to your SaaS app by securing a spot on Startup Leaderboard. Get a do-follow backlink to pump SEO rankings.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>Let's Focus</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/let-s-focus?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>Simple and powerful todo list that helps you get more done

A simple and powerful to-do list designed to help you get more done with ease. Whether you're managing daily tasks or tackling complex projects, it offers the tools you need to stay organized and productive. Optimized for individual who want to thrive.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>Gift.xyz</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/gift-xyz?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>Celebrate special moments forever.

Celebrate special moments forever. Collect your first! https://app.gift.xyz/giftxyz-live-on-product-hunt Why use Gift? - Can send to anyone anywhere instantly. - Can crowdfund from people all over the world to gift. - It’s immutable + yours forever.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item><item><title>Job Title Generator</title><link>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/job-title-generator?utm_campaign=producthunt-api&amp;utm_medium=api-v2&amp;utm_source=Application%3A+DailyHunter+%28ID%3A+140760%29</link><description>Need to Define a Job? Generate One in 10 seconds. 100% Free.

Create professional, tailored job titles in seconds with our Free Job Title Generator. Perfect for recruiters looking to attract top talent with clear, relevant titles. Easy to use and customizable for any industry or role.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate></item></channel></rss>